sriraj.org 2017-12-12

# Privacy policy and Terms of Usage

**Privacy Policy and Terms of Usage of Sriraj.org**

This website [Sriraj.org](http://www.sriraj.org/ "Sriraj.org") has a great respect towards the privacy of its valued visitors. But in order to constantly improve our services provided to you, we will collect some details about your visit to our website.

Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Sriraj.org, and how we safeguard your information.  You can rest assure that we’ll never share your details with any third parties.

**Log Files**

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files.  The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider), the browser (and its version) you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookie policy**

We use third party advertisements on Sriraj.org.  Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed.  This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (like showing Ads of Indian companies to Indians and US companies to visitors from US) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements).  This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).  The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey).  DART uses “non personally identifiable information”.  It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.  You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program.  Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Comment policy**

Although we highly recommend users to put their email addresses only in the email box provided and not in the comment box (so that they are not displayed publicly), we occasionally find users submitting their email addresses and telephone numbers along with the comment in the comment box. In such cases we reserve the right to either remove/edit some part of the comment so to protect our users from bots that scan websites for finding email addresses.

Also, users are encouraged to put their views via comments but before doing so, you must be sure that your comment is put in a good faith and doesn’t defame any person or Institution. If you do so, it is entirely your responsibility to face any consequences that may arise there of.

By using this website, you **agree** that you abide by the terms and policies stated above.
